Alvin Go

alvingogo25@gmail.com | (310) 766-3890 LinkedIn | Github | alvingo.com

Summary

Web Developer with 5 years experience in GIS and data analysis in the utility sector. Pursued interest for technology through coding. Passionate for building functional and user friendly interfaces. Values perseverance, dedication, and patience. Follower of sports and anything Disney.

Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Node, Express, Handlebars, React, SQL, MongoDB, Git, Responsive Design

Projects

TrackYoSelf / Front End Developer

May 2018

Journaling app that provides users with emotional analysis. Responsible for wireframing, creating, and styling the landing page, and the user dashboard. Built with React and styled with Materialize to make a clean and functional UI. Followed proper Git flow ensuring consistent code across all group members.

Clicky Memory / Web Developer

Apr 2018

Pixar themed memory game built with React that shuffles displayed characters for every guess. Uses React's state to store the characters and scores. Learned proper file structure within a React app.

Burger Time / Full Stack Developer

Apr 2018

Burger app using CRUD methods with SQL and a custom ORM. Users can add, eat, and remove burgers from the database. Front end built with Handlebars and simply designed with Flexbox.

Toy Story Trivia / Front End Developer

Feb 2018

Trivia game based on the Disney Pixar movie series Toy Story. Users have a set time to answer each question. Score is provided at the end of the game. Used Javascript and jQuery to build the game logic and run the game automatically.

Employment

ParkMe / Data Operations/Drive Tester

Feb 2016-Present

Aggregate parking data for use in car navigation systems, following strict syntax for display. Travel to various cities for ground truthing and KPI improvements. Hired, trained, and managed contractors for data collection.

Sasco / Field Auditor Jul 2015-Feb 2016

Performed multiple verification tests for potential small cell tower sites. Reported issues and improvements to software and collection methods. Trained employees in new markets on all collection methods.

UDC / Field Data/QA Technician

Jan 2014-Jun 2015

Traveled to remote locations for pole loading assessments within SoCal Edison's territory. Learned to be self-sufficient with assignments. Earned promotions from data collection to QA.

Processed aerial imagery for utility companies. Assisted a project in Australia managing a pilot and camera man to photo utility poles from a helicopter.

Education

UCLA Extension / Full Stack Web Development

Endured a 24 week intensive boot camp learning the fundamentals in web development, and building thoughtful web apps using the MERN stack.

University of California, Santa Barbara / BA Geography

Studied Geography with and emphasis in GIS. Produced projects tracking glacier movement using remote sensing with ENVI software. Learned basics of data visualizations with mapping using ArcGIS ESRI.